realauthor.com 2013-06-09

# Privacy Policy | RealAuthor.com

## Privacy Policy

1\. RealAuthor.com respects the privacy of its users and does not collect any personally identifiable user information without prior notice. Web statistics are the sole and private property of RealAuthor.com and are only used for troubleshooting purposes.

Information we collects  
2\. RealAuthor.com generally collects personally identifying information with your specific knowledge and consent. When you register to become a member of RealAuthor.com and subscribe to our services, you are asked to provide information, such as your e-mail address, name and/or other information.

Use of this information  
3\. RealAuthor.com uses this information to provide you with the service you have requested. For example, if you subscribe to any of our newspapers, we may use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice.  
4\. We may also use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services, or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.  
5\. We may allow access to our database by third parties that provide us with services, such as technical maintenance or forums and job search software, but only for the purpose of and to the extent necessary to provide those ervices. RealAuthor.com does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.

Cookies  
6\. RealAuthor.com may use cookies to keep some information that are placed by a Web site in a storage place on your own computer. We use cookies to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personalization information. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliated companies.  
7\. Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.  
8\. If you don’t want cookies stored on your computers, your Web browser would likely include an option that allows you to not accept cookies. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of RealAuthor.com may not function properly.

Ad Servers  
9\. To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies like Google (www.google.com/adsense), Kontera, Commission Junction, ClickBank etc. that place ads on our web site. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies, with the help of cookies, may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policy of each those websites. Privacy Policy of Google is available at http://www.google.com/privacy.html  
10\. While your individual information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use aggregated anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

Children  
11\. RealAuthor.com is not intended for use by minors or children, especially those under age 18. No one under age 18 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums and/or chats. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardians(s) before using our services, including registration and/or subscriptions to our services offered by this site.  
12\. If your children disclose information about themselves in our public discussion areas, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. RealAuthor.com cannot be held responsible for any action by your children while using our services, with or without your consents.

Links to other Web sites  
13\. This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

Revision of this Privacy Policy  
14\. This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time without any prior notice to the visitors. Continued access of RealAuthor.com by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy. It is the goal of RealAuthor.com to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy.

Contacting Us  
15\. This is the website of RealAuthor.com. We can be reached via e-mail at webmaster(at)RealAuthor.com. Please replace (at) with @. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above email address.
